{
  "AdsUrls": [

  ],
  "FeedbackTexts": [
    "Alright!",
    "Yeah!!",
    "Oh Yeah!!",
    "Wowww!!"
  ],
  "CongratulationsTexts": [
    "congratulation"
  ],  
  "Difficulty": {
    "Easy": [
      {
        "question": "The first cryptocurrency?",
        "answer": "BITCOIN"
      },
      {
        "question": "A digital currency from Ethereum?",
        "answer": "ETHER"
      },
      {
        "question": "A popular crypto meme coin?",
        "answer": "DOGE"
      },
      {
        "question": "The process of validating crypto transactions?",
        "answer": "MINING"
      },
      {
        "question": "Bitcoin's smallest unit?",
        "answer": "SATOSHI"
      },
      {
        "question": "How are Bitcoin transactions secured?",
        "answer": "HASHING"
      },
      {
        "question": "A place to store your crypto?",
        "answer": "WALLET"
      },
      {
        "question": "A popular stablecoin?",
        "answer": "USDTETHER"
      },
      {
        "question": "Cryptocurrency inspired by memes?",
        "answer": "SHIBA"
      },
      {
        "question": "An exchange without a central authority?",
        "answer": "DEX"
      },
      {
        "question": "A cryptocurrency derived from Bitcoin?",
        "answer": "LITECOIN"
      },
      {
        "question": "Digital collectibles on the blockchain?",
        "answer": "NFTS"
      },
      {
        "question": "A common Ethereum token standard?",
        "answer": "ERCSTANDARD"
      },
      {
        "question": "A reward for mining a block?",
        "answer": "REWARD"
      },
      {
        "question": "The term for a group of crypto transactions?",
        "answer": "BLOCK"
      },
      {
        "question": "Ethereum's native token?",
        "answer": "ETHER"
      },
      {
        "question": "Storing crypto offline is called?",
        "answer": "COLDWALLET"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a private key unlock?",
        "answer": "WALLET"
      },
    ],
    "Medium": [
      {
        "question": "Popular blockchain for DeFi projects?",
        "answer": "ETHEREUM"
      },
      {
        "question": "The process of verifying crypto transactions?",
        "answer": "CONSENSUS"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does PoW stand for?",
        "answer": "PROOFOFWORK"
      },
      {
        "question": "A cryptocurrency created by splitting from Bitcoin?",
        "answer": "BITCOINCASH"
      },
      {
        "question": "An initial coin offering?",
        "answer": "ICO"
      },
      {
        "question": "The first altcoin ever created?",
        "answer": "NAMECOIN"
      },
      {
        "question": "Ethereum's founder?",
        "answer": "VITALIK"
      },
      {
        "question": "A consensus algorithm in Ethereum?",
        "answer": "PROOFOFSTAKE"
      },
      {
        "question": "A privacy-focused cryptocurrency?",
        "answer": "MONERO"
      },
      {
        "question": "A token standard for NFTs?",
        "answer": "ERCSTANDARD"
      },
      {
        "question": "How are crypto transactions secured?",
        "answer": "HASHES"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Chainlink provide to smart contracts?",
        "answer": "DATA"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is used to verify transactions?",
        "answer": "SIGNATURES"
      },
      {
        "question": "Gas fees are paid in which currency?",
        "answer": "ETH"
      },
      {
        "question": "A crypto project for interoperability?",
        "answer": "POLKADOT"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main purpose of DeFi?",
        "answer": "FINANCE"
      },
      {
        "question": "A tool to store private keys?",
        "answer": "LEDGER"
      },
      {
        "question": "What runs decentralized apps?",
        "answer": "BLOCKCHAIN"
      },
      {
        "question": "A pseudonym for Bitcoin's creator?",
        "answer": "SATOSHI"
      },
      {
        "question": "A block explorer shows transaction?",
        "answer": "HISTORY"
      }
    ],
    "Hard": [
      {
        "question": "The consensus mechanism used by Bitcoin?",
        "answer": "PROOFOFWORK"
      },
      {
        "question": "The creator of Bitcoin?",
        "answer": "SATOSHI"
      },
      {
        "question": "An Ethereum upgrade to PoS?",
        "answer": "THEMERGE"
      },
      {
        "question": "A type of digital signature in crypto?",
        "answer": "ELLIPTIC"
      },
      {
        "question": "The process of splitting a blockchain?",
        "answer": "FORKING"
      },
      {
        "question": "The technique to scale blockchain?",
        "answer": "SHARDING"
      },
      {
        "question": "Crypto without a central issuer?",
        "answer": "DECENTRAL"
      },
      {
        "question": "Cryptographic process ensuring data security?",
        "answer": "ENCRYPTION"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where are crypto transactions recorded?",
        "answer": "LEDGER"
      },
      {
        "question": "A digital marketplace for NFTs?",
        "answer": "OPENSEA"
      },
      {
        "question": "Algorithm securing Bitcoin?",
        "answer": "SHAHASH"
      },
      {
        "question": "A synonym for blockchain forks?",
        "answer": "UPGRADES"
      },
      {
        "question": "The process to generate new tokens?",
        "answer": "MINTING"
      },
      {
        "question": "An organization run by smart contracts?",
        "answer": "DAO"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who validates PoS transactions?",
        "answer": "VALIDATORS"
      },
      {
        "question": "What locks funds in DeFi contracts?",
        "answer": "COLLATERAL"
      },
      {
        "question": "The term for a new coin offering?",
        "answer": "TOKENSALE"
      },
      {
        "question": "A blockchain bridge connects?",
        "answer": "NETWORKS"
      }
    ]
  }
}
